<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just notes</title>
    <description>Just notes</description>
    <link>https://netbros.com</link>
    
        <atom:link href="https://netbros.com/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://netbros.com/apple-icon-144x144.png</url>
      <title>notes</title>
      <link>https://netbros.com/categories/</link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>144</height>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-08 - 08:27:05-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A very dear friend of mine, Charles Smith, went in for liver surgery (cancer) at 08:00 EST. He is a good kid, with a loving wife, and a lovely very young child. We don&amp;rsquo;t want to lose him. Please keep him in your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:27:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638970025</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638970025</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-07 - 15:14:11-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Each time I find myself thinking, and trying to post something negative, or a downer, I slap my own self. Someone asked me today if I have been to the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:14:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638908051</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638908051</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-07 - 10:31:35-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Going on leave next week, which would be something irrelevant, and ordinary. Oh, no. It ain&amp;rsquo;t that easy! The pile of things I need to do before I go on leave is growing. Like, wow!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 10:31:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638891095</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638891095</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-06 - 15:50:15-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really wish to be wealthy&amp;mdash;though I would not say no to wealth&amp;mdash;but to have enough to tell off a few people, and go on with my life without having to worry about income.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems that those who care are frowned upon, and penalised. The rest go on with their lives in apparent bliss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 15:50:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638823815</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638823815</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-06 - 11:26:15-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Updates&amp;rdquo; about a technical issue every 30 minutes, that contain no updates, but the same noise over and over. 🤯&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 11:26:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638807975</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638807975</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-05 - 12:20:53-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sitting down to eat at Domu after over two years felt, well, a bit weird. We wanted take away, but that was not an option this time. Not was it delivery. We asked the server why, and he said they were &amp;ldquo;trying to get back to normal&amp;rdquo;. That&amp;rsquo;s rather weird because the pandemic ensues, and one could order take away, and delivery, &lt;strong&gt;before&lt;/strong&gt; COVID stroke. Go figure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 12:20:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638724853</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638724853</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-04 - 00:29:08-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This mortal form is growing weak. I need sustenance, then sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:29:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638595748</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638595748</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-03 - 18:58:48-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mum and dad still quarrel about little things. Both older than a $47,000 bottle of wine, and still quarrel about silly things. I told them today: &amp;ldquo;You both are old, and have been together for a lifetime. You know your quirks, what bother you, and not. If you quarrel because you are bored, and need the adrenaline rush a good quarrel brings, to feel alive, to give meaning to the day, then quarrel along! If not, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to stop this, and know that, as you age, things could&amp;mdash;and will most likely&amp;mdash;get worse. You will have less patience, you will tire easily, and have aches, which will get you grumpy, and shorten your fuse.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their house today as, when I am there, I am the mediator. First stop on my errants tomorrow? Their house.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 18:58:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638575928</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638575928</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-03 - 15:27:21-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have added the simple ability to reply to notes, by clicking on the note&amp;rsquo;s subject. I will pin this note for a little bit, so that it remain fresh for a while. I am not expecting replies, but being able to do so is here now, in case one is merited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note&amp;rsquo;s permalink can still be found on the date, and on the Note-ID.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 15:27:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638563241</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638563241</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-03 - 13:00:47-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that we are enjoying faster Internet connectivity speeds we have come to realise our Google WiFi mesh doesn&amp;rsquo;t really cut it. Even though we have four mesh devices, each with direct line of sight to each other, we are getting &amp;ldquo;weak connection&amp;rdquo; amongst them. We are also, almost constantly, connecting to the 2.4 GHz band instead of the faster 5 GHz one, and there is no way to control that on the devices themselves. In other words, and in plain English: they suck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I am looking to buy an enterprise grade WiFi router and mesh. Everything I have found requires cabling&amp;mdash;which is the obvious on an enterprise, but not in our non-CAT-X wired home. Hence, we are bound to consumer products. Any recommendations? I am eyeballing &lt;a href=&#34;https://store.amplifi.com/products/amplifi-alien-router-mesh&#34;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://shop.asus.com/us/rog/90ig03s1-ba1g0v-rog-rapture-gt-ac5300.html&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;&amp;mdash;on this one I will need to add a mesh&amp;mdash;but not quite decided yet. I have been reading a lot, but reviews can be so misleading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, I know, first world problems. 😔&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 13:00:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638554447</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638554447</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-01 - 19:49:20-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What would the simplest, and easiest way to style a blockquote on CSS be, so that it mimics the &amp;ldquo;old style&amp;rdquo; email reply quoting? Something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; This is a sentence here, that &lt;br&gt;
&amp;gt; looks like a quoted reply.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;gt; And this is another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ponder, I ponder, while looking Down Under&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 19:49:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638406160</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638406160</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-01 - 16:06:45-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have missed tea at mum&amp;rsquo;s for the last two days, because I have been going to visit, and taken care of, dad at the hospital. He is now home, and well, so&amp;hellip; missing tea no more. Off to shower, and to tea!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 16:06:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638392805</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638392805</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-12-01 - 14:03:04-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“If you want to, and even if you don&amp;rsquo;t, things are bound to happen. Earthlings call it fate.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 14:03:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638385384</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638385384</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-29 - 13:01:15-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a real test of sorts, but I am not sure how will it work, or if it will work as I want. The idea is to write notes mimicking an email. I am not quite there yet, but getting closer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:01:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1638208875</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1638208875</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-14 - 17:26:50-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From the episode &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://spongebob.fandom.com/wiki/The_Sponge_Who_Could_Fly&#34;&gt;The Sponge who could fly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo;, a nugget of wisdom:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need a plane to fly, plastic wings may make you cry&lt;br&gt;
Kites are made for windy days, lawn chairs with balloons fly away&lt;br&gt;
Inflatable pants you may as well skip&lt;br&gt;
If you want to fly, all you need is friendship.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SpongeBob SquarePants, always wise. So much to learn for him!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 17:26:50 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636928810</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636928810</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-11 - 19:51:36-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This one is short, and only to say &amp;ldquo;👋🏻 Claudine!&amp;rdquo; ☺️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:51:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636678296</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636678296</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-11 - 12:01:42-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think this qualifies as a small speed bump, right? It is not much about speed, but latency. If it remains that low, it is certainly a mission accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://netbros.com/posts/1636650101//img/1636650101.png&#34; alt=&#34;New broadband speed&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 12:01:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636650102</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636650102</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-10 - 19:55:24-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Went to Hotel Mum (mum&amp;rsquo;s house, LOL), and took a shower. Oh, what a wonderful feeling! I would happily go one day, or more, without eating, but having a luxurious shower is priceless. Onto binging now!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 19:55:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636592124</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636592124</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-10 - 18:08:17-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It truly was a long day&amp;mdash;started at 06:00, ended at 17:00&amp;mdash;but now it is over. As I was ending my shift, and were almost dressed as I came to this world, I realised there was no water coming from the shower. Turns out there is an outage in my area 😩. Now I am tired, filthy, and itchy. Amanda, the nice representative at the utilities company, told me they don&amp;rsquo;t have an estimate on when the water will flow once more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh dear, oh dear.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:08:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636585697</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636585697</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-10 - 11:53:29-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Upgrading these HPE servers firmware is like watching slow drying paint dry. A total, royal, pain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:53:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636563209</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636563209</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-10 - 09:52:00-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last working day of the week for me. Lots of things to do today, kinda overwhelming, but we can do this! Let&amp;rsquo;s get it over with, and bask into doing nothing afterwards. Yes, it will be a staycation about nothing but&amp;hellip; ain&amp;rsquo;t that something?!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636555920</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636555920</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 21:53:47-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am so confussed with the RSS generation on this little experiment here. On Reeder, it only shows the title, no description. That is not the way it is supposed to be.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 21:53:47 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636512827</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636512827</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 20:36:50-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, T-Mobile offers a free year of Paramount Plus. I go through the hoops, create my Paramount+ account, and add the T-Mo discount. It tells me I can cancel at any time, and that it will run until current subscription expires (which should be November 2022). I cancel because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget and get charged due to my senility. What happens next, you ask? Well, I only have a week of subscription, nothing else. Oh, and I can&amp;rsquo;t apply the coupon T-Mo gave me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for nothing, T-Mo and Paramount!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 20:36:50 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636508210</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636508210</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 18:58:17-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mum and dad need a new auto. Theirs is over 20 years old and, well, it&amp;rsquo;s starting to tell them it had enought. It&amp;rsquo;s doing so in very certain ways, ways it knows it hurts. Like breaking badly, and costing hundreds of notes for repairs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 18:58:17 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636502297</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636502297</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 16:09:41-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Because I have come across this many times since the time changed last weekend: this is not daylight savings time, this is &amp;ldquo;regular&amp;rdquo; time. Daylight savings time is what we left behind&amp;mdash;and what many, many, many agree we should stop using. We gained the hour we lost thanks to DST. So, screw DST! Clear now?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:09:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636492181</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636492181</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 15:50:03-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Final dump, or spam. AT&amp;amp;T Fibre is coming this Thursday. Hopefully that latency, that slight delay that seems to take minutes, which get us killed (boom, head shot!) will stop. We simply can&amp;rsquo;t keep up living&amp;mdash;or dying&amp;mdash;like this.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:50:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636491003</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636491003</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 15:46:26-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;If wisdom ways you wisely seek, five things observe with care:&lt;br&gt;
to whom you speak, of whom you speak, and how, when and where.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ain&amp;rsquo;t that the truth! Though some people, and even ourselves, sometimes simply don&amp;rsquo;t care.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:46:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636490786</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636490786</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 15:39:06-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A four days weekend approaches. Yet, as I have done before&amp;mdash;and will do many, hopefully, times again&amp;mdash;I will have to mow the lawn, and do other secular chores, as always. It never ends! Well, it does, but we don&amp;rsquo;t really like it when it does.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:39:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636490346</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636490346</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021-11-09 - 15:20:15-0500</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, here we are, and here we go again. Nothing lasts forever. Nothing I do lasts for more than a month. So, here I am with the hopes this one will last longer, like, maybe two months? Anyway, cheers to a new beginning!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 15:20:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <link>https://netbros.com/#1636489215</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://netbros.com/#1636489215</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>